Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Bulgaria, 9
  - News releases, C
    - Bulgaria: Casual violence and illegal acts by police officers become widespread., 6 June 1996; (EUR 15/09/96); C11 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International gravely concerned about proposal to lift moratorium on executions., 13 June 1996; (EUR 15/12/96); C12 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International urges government to provide further information on human rights violations., 7 November 1996; (EUR 15/17/97); C13 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Government should prevent further deaths in children's homes., 6 March 1997; (EUR 15/02/97); C14 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International urges National Assembly to ensure draft law on alternative service is in line with international principles., 4 February 1998; (EUR 15/04/98); C15 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: abolition of the death penalty - a step forward in human rights protection., 11 December 1998; (EUR 15/21/98); C16 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: shooting and burning - rough justice for Roma teenagers., 16 August 2000; (EUR 15/04/00); C17 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bulgaria: Disabled woman condemned to 'slow death'., 10 October 2001; (EUR 15/02/01); C18 (Microfiche 306)
    - Bulgaria: Residents of Dragash Voyvoda are dying as a result of gross neglect., 15 April 2002; (EUR 15/04/02); C19 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Program of the International Forum on Discrimination of People with Mental Disabilities., 2 October 2002; (EUR 15/11/02); C20 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Systematic discrimination against people with mental disabilities., 3 October 2002; (EUR 15/12/02); C21 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Summary of Amnesty International's concerns regarding the treatment of people with mental disabilities., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/13/02); C22 (Microfiche 324)
    - A Life Worse than Imprisonment: Meeting Bulgaria's Mentally Disabled., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/15/02); C23 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Background to methodology., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/16/02); C24 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: People with mental disabilities hidden far from the eyes of society., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/17/02); C25 (Microfiche 324)
    - International Forum on Discrimination of People with Mental Disabilities. Opening remarks by Irene Khan, Secretary General, Amnesty International Sofia, 10 October 2002., (EUR 15/18/02); C26 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: The government should reject US impunity agreement., 13 May 2003; (EUR 15/003/03); C27 (Microfiche 349)
    - Libya: Quash death sentences against foreign medical professionals., 6 May 2004; (MDE 19/09/04); C28 (Microfiche 373)
    - Bulgaria and Romania: EU must address outstanding human rights concerns., 19 October 2005; (EUR 02/002/2005); C29 (Microfiche 397)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Reports of brutality in Bulgarian prison camp., 1/1976; D1 (Microfiche 1)
    - Vladimir Y Makarov (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 3/1976; D2 (Microfiche 1)
    - Christo Kolev-Jordanov (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 6/1976; D3 (Microfiche 1)
    - Amnesty International appeals against Bulgarian death sentence., 6/1976; D4 (Microfiche 1)
    - Ljuben Georgiev and Anastasia Hadji-Dimitrov (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 5/1977; D5 (Microfiche 1)
    - Stefan Wladimirov Gusenko (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 3/1978; D6 (Microfiche 1)
    - Former AI-adoptee re-arrested in Bulgaria., 9/1978; D7 (Microfiche 1)
    - Petr Kondofersky (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 11/1978; D8 (Microfiche 1)
    - News of past campaigns: Petr Kondofersky., 7/1979; D9 (Microfiche 1)
    - Dimiter Kolev (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 1/1980; D10 (Microfiche 22)
    - News of past campaigns: Dimiter Kolev., 5/1980; D11 (Microfiche 22)
    - Release of Dimiter Kolev., 8/1980; D12 (Microfiche 22)
    - Kiril Spasov (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 3/1985; D13 (Microfiche 57)
    - Ethnic Turks jailed during name-changing campaign in Bulgaria., 9/1985; D14 (Microfiche 57)
    - Reprisals against ethnic minority., 12/1985; D15 (Microfiche 57)
    - Bulgaria: Imprisonment of ethnic Turks., 4/1986; D16 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgarians react to Amnesty International report., 6/1986; D17 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Kiril Spasov (Prisoners of the Month 1985)., 8/1986; D18 (Microfiche 66)
    - Detained after refusing to change his name (appeal case)., 10/1986; D19 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Authorities contest Amnesty International's evidence of abuses., 11/1986; D20 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Kostadin Kalmakov (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 12/1986; D21 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Human rights abuses against ethnic Turks., 8/1987; D22 (Microfiche 77)
    - Bulgaria: Kostadin Kalmakov (Prisoners of the Month 1986: Update)., 8/1987; D23 (Microfiche 77)
    - Bulgaria: Ibraim Ismailov Arifov: 48-year- old doctor, one of four people recently sentenced to up to 10 years' imprisonment for protesting against the forced assimilation of the ethnic Turkish minority (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 1/1988; D24 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: Emil Kostadin Kalmakov and Kostadin Angelov Kalmakov., 6/1988; AI Focus on conscientious objection.; D25 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International mission., 11/1988; D26 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: Ismail Mehmedov Hyuseyinov: a 34-year-old ethnic Turk, he was arrested in May 1985 and has been banished to a village in northwest Bulgaria for refusing to change his name (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 3/1989; D27 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Ibraim Ismailov Arifov still in prison., 7/1989; Focus (Update on Prisoners of the Month 1988).; D28 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Ethnic Turks are killed and beaten., 8/1989; D29 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Human rights activists detained and harassed., 11/1989; D30 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: prisoners of conscience amnestied., 2/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter, February 1990.; D31 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria: Ethnic Turks arrested., 3/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter March 1990.; D32 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria: Ibrahim Ismailov Arifov and Kostadin Ivanov released., 4/1990; AI Newsletter April 1990.; D33 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria: Enver Ahmedov Hatibov., 6/1990; Campaign for prisoners of the month, Amnesty International Newsletter, June 1990.; D34 (Microfiche 110)
    - Executions suspended in Bulgaria., 11/1990; Amnesty International Newsletter, November 1990.; D35 (Microfiche 110)
    - Human rights violations in Europe: Bulgaria., 8/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, August 1991 (Focus on Europe).; D35 (Microfiche 119)
    - No. 36 not used., D36
    - Bulgaria: Man dies in police custody (Slavcho Lyubenov Tsonchev)., 1 December 1994; Amnesty International Newsletter December 1994.; (NWS 21/12/94); D37 (Microfiche 167)
    - Bulgaria: Police violence rife as lawlessness spreads., 1 July 1996; (NWS 21/07/96); D38 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Worldwide appeals: Residents of Dragash Voyvoda are dying as a result of gross neglect., 1 June 2002; The Wire, June 2002. Vol. 32, No. 5.; (NWS 21/05/02); D39 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Unfit for human habitation, brutal conditions for people with mental disabilities in Bulgaria., 1 October 2002; The Wire, October 2002. Vol. 32, No. 08.; (NWS 21/08/02); D40 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Worldwide appeals: Bulgaria: Children in care home need help:\., 1 August 2004; The Wire, August 2004. Vol. 34, No. 7.; (NWS 21/07/04); D41 (Microfiche 373)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Bulgaria: arrest, trial and imprisonment: background information on legal provisions and their application in cases known to Amnesty International., 28/4/1981; (EUR 15/02/81); E1 (Microfiche 31)
    - Amnesty law passed in Bulgaria., 15/7/1981; (EUR 15/03/81); E2 (Microfiche 31)
    - Ethnic minorities in rural areas. (Extract), 11/10/1982; (ACT 31/03/82); E3 (Microfiche 31)
    - Intolerance and discrimination on grounds of religion or belief. (Extract), 11/1984; (POL 03/05/84); E4 (Microfiche 48)
    - 500 ethnic Turks reportedly killed., 28/2/1985; Weekly update service 7/85.; (NWS 01/07/85); E5 (Microfiche 57)
    - Imprisonment and reported extrajudicial execution of ethnic Turks in Bulgaria., 16/8/1985; (EUR 15/04/85); E6 (Microfiche 57)
    - Violations of the human rights of ethnic minorities in Bulgaria., 5/9/1985; oral statement by Amnesty International to the United Nations Sub-Commission on Prevention of Discrimination and Protection on Minorities (38th session, Geneva, 5-30 August 1985).; (IOR 41/08/85); E7 (Microfiche 57)
    - List of ethnic Turks reported imprisoned or killed. Background to cases of Sebatin Mahmudov Aliov and Osman Hatibov., 14/2/1986; (EUR 15/02/86); E8 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Imprisonment and deaths in name-changing campaign., 4/1986; Trade Union Bulletin 28.; (ACT 73/03/86); E9 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Imprisonment of ethnic Turks., 4/1986; Action Bulletin.; (ACT 08/04/86); E10 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria., 4/1986; The imprisonment of persons seeking to leave a country or to return to their own country.; (POL 03/02/86); E11 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria., 5/1986; Religious Intolerance.; (POL 03/03/86); E12 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Bulgarian Telegraph Agency comments on Amnesty International report., 4/6/1986; Weekly update service 17/86.; (NWS 01/17/86); E13 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Omer Mustafov Kochandzhiev., 7/1986; Amnesty International Week 1986 Forgotten Prisoners'' Appeal cases.; (ACT 31/01/86); E14 (Microfiche 66)
    - Bulgaria: Continuing human rights abuses against ethnic Turks., 7/1987; (EUR 15/01/87); E15 (Microfiche 77)
    - Bulgaria: Detained doctor: Dr Ibraim Ismailov Arifov., 29/2/1988; (EUR 15/01/88); E16 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria., 2/1988; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/88); E17 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: Embassies react to Newsletter article on Ibraim Ismailov Arifov., 28/5/1988; Weekly Update Service 19/88.; (NWS 11/19/88); E18 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: Discussion of mental abnormality and the death penalty., 8/1988; Death Penalty News.; (ACT 53/08/88); E19 (Microfiche 87)
    - Bulgaria: At least three ethnic Turks die during demonstrations., 1/6/1989; Weekly Update Service 21/89.; (NWS 11/21/89); E20 (Microfiche 97)
    - Ethnic Turk protests in Bulgaria., 22/6/1989; Weekly Update Service 24/89.; (NWS 11/24/89); E21 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Disappearance'' of Konstantin Trenchev, underground trade union movement leader., 7/1989; Trade Union Bulletin 41.; (ACT 73/08/89); E22 (Microfiche 97)
    - Ethnic Turks protest in Bulgaria., 24/8/1989; Weekly Update Service 34/89.; (NWS 11/34/89); E23 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Imprisonment of ethnic Turks and human rights activists., 2/1989; (EUR 15/01/89); E24 (Microfiche 97)
    - Bulgaria: Moratorium on executions., 10/1990; Death Penalty News, October 1990.; (ACT 53/06/90); E25 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria: Ethnic Turks and other muslims., 2/1990; (EUR 15/01/90); E26 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International's remaining concerns regarding ethnic Turks in Bulgaria., 3/1990; (EUR 15/03/90); E27 (Microfiche 110)
    - Bulgaria., 1/1991; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/91); E28 (Microfiche 119)
    - Bulgaria: Parliament to vote on death penalty., 7/2/1991; Weekly Update Service 05/91.; (NWS 11/05/91); E29 (Microfiche 119)
    - Bulgaria: Scheduled trial of former head of state., 20/2/1991; Weekly Update Service 07/91.; (NWS 11/07/91); E30 (Microfiche 119)
    - Bulgaria: Releases of political prisoners., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe November 1990 - April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E31 (Microfiche 119)
    - Bulgaria: Allegations of torture remain uninvestigated., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E32 (Microfiche 119)
    - Bulgaria: Moves towards abolition., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E33 (Microfiche 133-134)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International visit to encourage membership., 13/5/1992; Weekly Update Service 19/92.; (NWS 11/19/92); E34 (Microfiche 134)
    - Bulgaria: ratifications., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E35 (Microfiche 134)
    - Bulgaria: alleged torture and ill-treatment of Roma in Pazardjik., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E36 (Microfiche 134)
    - Bulgaria: ratifications., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E37 (Microfiche 134)
    - Bulgaria: Ill-treatment of Anton Stefanov Assenov and Stefan Assenov Ivanov., 9 March 1993; (EUR 15/01/93); E38 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Torture of Khristo Nedialkov Khristov., 8 April 1993; (EUR 15/02/93); E39 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Torture and ill-treatment of Roma., 1 May 1993; (EUR 15/03/93); E40 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Allegations of torture and ill-treatment of Roma., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E41 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Alleged torture of Zaharie Aleksandrov Stefanov., 6 August 1993; (EUR 15/04/93); E42 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: The alleged torture and other ill-treatment of nine Roma in Stara Zagora., 24 September 1993; (EUR 15/05/93); E43 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Conscientious objectors may be prosecuted and imprisoned for evasion of military service., 18 October 1993; Amnesty International News Service 135/93.; (NWS 11/135/93); E44 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria., 1 November 1993; Statement on torture in CSCE states. Statements to the CSCE Human Dimension Implementation Meeting, Warsaw, 27 September - 15 October 1993.; (IOR 52/03/93); E45 (Microfiche 150)
    - Bulgaria: Allegations of torture and ill-treatment; conscientious objection to military service; ratifications., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E46 (Microfiche 167)
    - Bulgaria: Possibility of lifting of moratorium., 1 March 1994; Death Penalty News March 1994.; (ACT 53/01/94); E47 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Racial attacks against the Roma community of Dolno Belotintsi., 23 March 1994; (EUR 15/01/94); E48 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Torture and ill-treatment of Roma in Glushnik., 6 April 1994; (EUR 15/02/94); E49 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Racial attacks against the Roma in Pleven., 6 April 1994; (EUR 15/03/94); E50 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Torture and ill-treatment of Roma continues., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E51 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Ill-treatment of Anton Stefanov Assenov, aged 14., 1 July 1994; AI Week 1994: cases for appeals.; (ACT 31/02/94) (includes photograph); E52 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Turning a blind eye to racism., 1 September 1994; (EUR 15/04/94); E53 (Microfiche 168)
    - Bulgaria: Allegations of torture and ill-treatment of Roma., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E54 (Microfiche 186)
    - Bulgaria: Ill-treatment of local protesters in Sapareva Banya., 21 February 1995; (EUR 15/01/95); E55 (Microfiche 186)
    - Bulgaria: Excessive use of force by members of special forces during police raid in Sofia., 4 April 1995; (EUR 15/02/95); E56 (Microfiche 186)
    - Bulgaria: Reported unlawful killing of Angel Anguelov and ill-treatment of Atanas and Alexander Anguelov., 24 April 1995; (EUR 15/03/95); E57 (Microfiche 186)
    - Bulgaria: Death of a Rom in suspicious circumstances; police ill-treatment in Sapareva Banya and Sofia., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E58 (Microfiche 186)
    - Bulgaria: Alleged ill-treatment by Bulgarian special police forces in the Druzhba quarter and Rakovski stadium in Sofia., 12 February 1996; (EUR 15/02/96); E59 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E60 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: The reported ill-treatment and death in suspicious circumstances of Iliya Gherginov., 19 March 1996; (EUR 15/05/96); E61 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: The reported ill-treatment of Iliya Assenov Lambov by police officers., 3 May 1996; (EUR 15/06/96); E62 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Shootings, deaths in custody, torture and ill-treatment., 6 June 1996; (EUR 15/07/96); E63 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: Alleged ill-treatment by Bulgarian special police forces in Sofia., 17 June 1996; (EUR 15/11/96); E64 (Microfiche 206)
    - Bulgaria: The reported ill-treatment of Anton Mitkov Dimitrov., 24 June 1996; (EUR 15/13/96); E65 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria: Moratoria on executions., 1 July 1996; Abolition of the death penalty worldwide: developments in 1995.; (ACT 50/07/96); E66 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria: Bulgarian authorities respond to Amnesty International's June 1996 report., 1 October 1996; (EUR 15/16/96); E67 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E68 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria: The reported ill-treatment and death under suspicious circumstances of Angel Zubchikov., 28 November 1996; (EUR 15/19/96); E69 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria: Prisoner of conscience: conscientious objector Dian Yankov Dimitrov., 20 December 1996; (EUR 15/21/96); E70 (Microfiche 207)
    - Bulgaria: The reported ill-treatment of Valentina and Nedyalko Zagorov and Pavlina and Georgi Pehlivanov., 19 March 1997; (EUR 15/04/97); E71 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria., 15 April 1997; Out of the margins: the right to conscientious objection to military service in Europe.; (EUR 01/02/97); E72 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Moratoria on executions., 1 June 1997; The death penalty worldwide: developments in 1996.; (ACT 50/05/97); E73 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Reported ill-treatment by officers of the Special Forces unit in Neron-2 discotheque and Biblioteka club in Sofia., 21 July 1997; (EUR 15/07/97); E74 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Prisoner of conscience., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E75 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Reported ill-treatment of Roma in the Montana region., 1 September 1997; (EUR 15/09/97); E76 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Reported ill-treatment of Zlatko Radev Gulekov by police officers., 9 September 1997; (EUR 15/10/97); E77 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Growing incidence of unlawful use of firearms by law enforcement officials., 1 October 1997; (EUR 15/12/97); E78 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Growing incidence of unlawful use of firearms by police., 1 November 1997; AI Concerns in Europe: July-October 1997 Supplement.; (EUR 01/07/97); E79 (Microfiche 225)
    - Bulgaria: Death in suspicious circumstances of Mincho Sartmachev and reported torture of Stanimir Georgiev., 21 January 1998; (EUR 15/01/98); E80 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: Prosecution of journalists for defaming public officials; new cases of shootings, deaths in custody, tortur and ill-treatment., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E81 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: Medical letter writing action: Death in custody and torture., 3 February 1998; (EUR 15/03/98); E82 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: New reports of unlawful use of firearms by law enforcement officials., 6 February 1998; (EUR 15/05/98); E83 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria., 1 April 1998; The death penalty worldwide: Developments in 1997.; (ACT 50/04/98); E84 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: Alleged ill-treatment of Tsetska Blagoeva by police officers in the Montana region., 17 August 1998; (EUR 15/18/98); E85 (Microfiche 243)
    - Bulgaria: New cases of ill-treatment of Roma., 18 August 1998; (EUR 15/11/98); E86 (Microfiche 243-244)
    - Bulgaria: New cases of shootings, deaths in suspicious circumstances, torture and ill-treatment; conscientious objection to military service., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E87 (Microfiche 244)
    - Bulgaria: Romani children beaten by police., 1 November 1998; Juvenile justice: Every child's basic human right.; (ACT 76/04/98); E88 (Microfiche 244)
    - Bulgaria: Recent reports of unlawful use of firearms by law enforcement officials., 1 December 1998; (EUR 15/19/98); E89 (Microfiche 244)
    - Bulgaria: Krassimir Nikolov Savov: prisoner of conscience., 1 January 1999; (EUR 15/01/99); E90 (Microfiche 262-263)
    - Bulgaria: Total abolition in Bulgaria, Canada and Lithuania., 1 January 1999; Death Penalty News: December 1998.; (ACT 53/01/99); E91 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria., 1 April 1999; Concerns in Europe July-December 1998.; (EUR 01/01/99); E92 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria: Countries which abolished the death penalty in 1998., 1 May 1999; The Death Penalty Worldwide: Developments in 1998.; (ACT 50/04/99); E93 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria: International treaties., 1 June 1999; Death Penalty News June 1999.; (ACT 53/03/99); E94 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria: The UN Committee against Torture meets to consider Bulgaria's second periodic report., 1 August 1999; Concerns in Europe January - June 1999.; (EUR 01/02/99); E95 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria: Ratification of Second Optional Protocol to the ICCPR., 1 September 1999; Death Penalty News September 1999.; (ACT 53/04/99); E96 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria: Fuelling the flames of conflict., 1 October 1999; The Terror Trade Times: Focus on Africa.; (ACT 31/02/99); E97 (Microfiche 263)
    - Bulgaria., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E98 (Microfiche 284)
    - Bulgaria: The shooting Atanas Djambazov, a 14 year old Roma boy., 16 August 2000; (EUR 15/01/00); E99 (Microfiche 284-285)
    - Bulgaria: Tsvetalin Perov, a 16 year-old boy, severely burned in police detention., 16 August 2000; (EUR 15/03/00); E100 (Microfiche 285)
    - Bulgaria., 21 August 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe: January - June 2000.; (EUR 01/03/00); E101 (Microfiche 285)
    - Bulgaria., 1 March 2001; Concerns in Europe July-December 2000.; (EUR 01/01/01); E102 (Microfiche 306)
    - Bulgaria., 1 September 2001; Concerns in Europe January - June 2001.; (EUR 01/03/01); E103 (Microfiche 306)
    - Bulgaria: Sanadinovo: This is truly a ghastly place''., 11 April 2002; (EUR 15/02/02); E104 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria., 30 May 2002; Concerns in Europe Bulletin: July - December 2001.; (EUR 01/02/02); E105 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria: Mission highlights: Bulgaria., 1 June 2002; Amnesty International Annual Review 2001.; (ORG 10/02/02); E106 (Microfiche 324)
    - Bulgaria., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E107 (Microfiche 325)
    - Bulgaria: Amnesty International's Concerns and Recommendations to the Bulgarian government., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/07/02); E108 (Microfiche 325)
    - Bulgaria: Arbitrary detention and ill-treatment of people with mental disabilities., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/08/02); E109 (Microfiche 325)
    - Bulgaria: Arbitrary detention and ill-treatment of people with mental disabilities: Appeals cases., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/10/02); E110 (Microfiche 325)
    - Bulgaria: Far from the eyes of society: Systematic discrimination against people with mental disabilities., 10 October 2002; (EUR 15/05/02); E111 (Microfiche 325-326)
    - Bulgaria: Open letter to the Foreign Minister of Bulgaria urging rejection of the impunity agreement with the United States of America on the International Criminal Court., 13 May 2003; (EUR 15/004/03); E112 (Microfiche 349)